<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal">
    <x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <focus_area>education</focus_area>
        <notes/>
        <participation>yes</participation>
        <potential_impact><![CDATA[<p><span><span style="font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &#39;Segoe UI&#39;, system-ui, &#39;Apple Color Emoji&#39;, &#39;Segoe UI Emoji&#39;, &#39;Segoe UI Web&#39;, sans-serif; font-size: 14px; white-space: pre-wrap;">By creating a single digital platform to connect surplus educational resources with students in need, we can reduce waste, improve equitable access to technology and learning materials, and empower underserved communities.<br />The solution will help bridge the digital divide by redirecting hundreds of unused devices, books, and course licenses to students who need them most resulting in improved academic participation, better digital literacy, and reduced learning gaps. By creating a single digital platform to connect surplus educational resources with students in need, we can reduce waste, improve equitable access to technology and learning materials, and empower underserved communities.<br />The solution will help bridge the digital divide by redirecting hundreds of unused devices, books, and course licenses to students who need them most resulting in improved academic participation, better digital literacy, and reduced learning gaps. </span></span></p>]]></potential_impact>
        <problem_statement>Schools, libraries, and corporates often have unused learning assets including  surplus laptops, e-books, tutoring hours, or unused online course licenses while under-resourced students lack access to quality learning.&#13;
The main barrier is the absence of a quick and transparent communication channel that matches available resources with nearby students or institutions in need.</problem_statement>
        <project_name>SkillBridge </project_name>
        <solution_proposal><![CDATA[<h2><strong>How do you envision the ideal solution to this  problem?</strong></h2>
<p> </p>
<h3>Which ServiceNow products or capabilities would be used?</h3>
<p></p><p>I see this below products form ServiceNow helps this initiative,</p>
<p><span>• <strong>Now Mobile / Service Portal:</strong> Donors post a “Learning Resource Available” (e.g., 20 surplus tablets, tutoring hours) in under 30 seconds. <br />• <strong>Workflow Studio / Flow Designer</strong>: Automates alerts to the closest registered schools or NGOs and manages a “claim” workflow to avoid double allocation.<br />• <strong>App Engine Studio</strong>: Custom tables for Donors, Recipients, Resources, and Requests to capture key details.<br />• <strong>Platform Analytics</strong>: Dashboards to show students served, devices/books distributed, tutoring hours delivered for program managers.<br />• <strong>Knowledge Management</strong>: Guides and FAQs for teachers, parents, and volunteers.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<hr style="border-top: 3px solid #bbb;" />
<h3>Are there any technical dependencies for the proposed solution?</h3>
<p></p><p><span>1. Mapping Service Integration: (e.g., Google Maps) to calculate distance between donors and recipients for fast pickup.<br />2. Notification Services: Push notifications (mobile) and SMS gateway (like Twilio) to alert recipients instantly.<br />3. Digital Signature Integration: (e.g., DocuSign) for secure confirmation of device or voucher hand-off.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<hr style="border-top: 3px solid #bbb;" />
<h3>What challenges would you foresee in implementing this idea?</h3>
<p></p><p><span>• Adoption Barrier: Need critical mass of both donors and recipients to sustain engagement.<br />• Trust &amp; Verification: Ensuring genuine recipients for high-value assets like laptops.<br />• Logistics: Platform connects supply with demand, but physical delivery still requires local partners or volunteers.</span></p>]]></solution_proposal>
        <state>submitted</state>
        <sys_class_name>x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-10-01 17:21:04</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>af29310e83d472106705c710feaad36f</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>1</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>SkillBridge </sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Hack4Good Idea Submission" source="x_snc_hack4good_0">95b5d2b7938832108543b2597bba109c</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Hack4Good Idea Submission">95b5d2b7938832108543b2597bba109c</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal_af29310e83d472106705c710feaad36f</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-10-01 17:21:08</sys_updated_on>
    </x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal>
</record_update>
