<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal">
    <x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <focus_area>cure</focus_area>
        <notes/>
        <participation>yes</participation>
        <potential_impact><![CDATA[<p>This way an organization can manage/track corporate domestic/international travels for its employees easily without the need of multiple separate applications for various phases of the travel requests raised by the employees.</p>]]></potential_impact>
        <problem_statement>All big Organizations need to plan/manage their employees' domestic/international corporate travels and typically they use different separate applications to raise travel requests, track the requests, request for VISAs and book the tickets etc.&#13;
Organizations can use their ServiceNow platform to have an application where an employee can raise travel request, which goes for approvals and post necessary approvals travel team can manage/track the request in ServiceNow. The team can be redirected to VISA portal for applying for VISA (if required) and to the approved travel booking sites for booking travel tickets/hotels and all.&#13;
&#13;
Management can have reports on quarterly/half-yearly/yearly basis to have sufficient budget allocated on travel expenses.</problem_statement>
        <project_name>Integrated Corporate Travel Management</project_name>
        <solution_proposal><![CDATA[<h2><strong>How do you envision the ideal solution to this  problem?</strong></h2>
<p> </p>
<h3>Which ServiceNow products or capabilities would be used?</h3>
<p></p><p>Now Mobile/Service catalog – for employees to raise travel requests and track those throughout the lifecycle.</p>
<p>Workspace – for travel team to work on different phases of the travel requests.</p>
<p>Integration/Integration hub– to integrate with approved travel booking site and relevant VISA portals.</p>
<p>Knowledge Management – to store knowledge guides, policies, best practices.</p>
<p>Notifications (Push/SMS) – to notify employees when the status of any request changes or gets approved till the tickets are booked and getting all the necessary staffs to travel.</p>
<p>Platform Analytics – to report on the travel requests and expenses for the organization to plan its travel budget.</p>
<p> </p>
<hr style="border-top: 3px solid #bbb;" />
<h3>Are there any technical dependencies for the proposed solution?</h3>
<p></p><p>NA</p>
<p> </p>
<hr style="border-top: 3px solid #bbb;" />
<h3>What challenges would you foresee in implementing this idea?</h3>
<p></p><p>NA</p>]]></solution_proposal>
        <state>submitted</state>
        <sys_class_name>x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-10-05 06:53:24</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>5540141bc398f210b541bb45990131d9</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>1</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>Integrated Corporate Travel Management</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Hack4Good Idea Submission" source="x_snc_hack4good_0">95b5d2b7938832108543b2597bba109c</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Hack4Good Idea Submission">95b5d2b7938832108543b2597bba109c</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal_5540141bc398f210b541bb45990131d9</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-10-05 06:53:25</sys_updated_on>
    </x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal>
</record_update>
