<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal">
    <x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <focus_area>other</focus_area>
        <notes/>
        <participation>yes</participation>
        <potential_impact><![CDATA[<p>Digital Teams Connect Management, being the digital communicator, will help teams to meet/communicate with just having one more store app or plugins installed in ServiceNow platform itself, minimizing more licensing costs  for having any separate communicator from another vendor. </p>]]></potential_impact>
        <problem_statement>Modern organizations has already evolved now to use digital communicators like Zoom or Microsoft teams for having internal connects/meetings among employees where earlier they used to use IP based phones as communicator. &#13;
ServiceNow can have this similar digital communicator developed as a new store application/plugin in ServiceNow as well through which we can communicate among team members by scheduling meetings and joining there. &#13;
It can also have additional features like recording the meeting and storing in ServiceNow (or in any on premise storage system) so that if someone can't join a meeting can revisit the recordings later.&#13;
&#13;
This way organization using ServiceNow will not require any separate communicator rather just having one more store app or plugins installed in ServiceNow platform itself minimizing more licensing costs.</problem_statement>
        <project_name>Digital Teams Connect Management</project_name>
        <solution_proposal><![CDATA[<h2><strong>How do you envision the ideal solution to this  problem?</strong></h2>
<p> </p>
<h3>Which ServiceNow products or capabilities would be used?</h3>
<p></p><p>Now Mobile and Workspace – for employees to schedule meetings and join meetings or having chats.</p>
<p>Integration/Integration hub– to integrate with Microsoft outlook as calendar invite, and with internal storage system to store the recorded meetings.</p>
<p>Notifications (Push/SMS) – to notify participants when a meeting is scheduled along with meeting details.</p>
<p> </p>
<hr style="border-top: 3px solid #bbb;" />
<h3>Are there any technical dependencies for the proposed solution?</h3>
<p></p><p>NA</p>
<p> </p>
<hr style="border-top: 3px solid #bbb;" />
<h3>What challenges would you foresee in implementing this idea?</h3>
<p></p><p>NA</p>]]></solution_proposal>
        <state>submitted</state>
        <sys_class_name>x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-10-05 13:12:37</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>1462659fc3503610b541bb4599013166</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>1</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>Digital Teams Connect Management</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Hack4Good Idea Submission" source="x_snc_hack4good_0">95b5d2b7938832108543b2597bba109c</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Hack4Good Idea Submission">95b5d2b7938832108543b2597bba109c</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal_1462659fc3503610b541bb4599013166</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-10-05 13:12:38</sys_updated_on>
    </x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal>
</record_update>
