<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal">
    <x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <focus_area>other</focus_area>
        <notes/>
        <participation>yes</participation>
        <potential_impact><![CDATA[<h2>For Non-Profits</h2>
<p>The app could measure the monetary value of donated services. The app could also track the project completion rates, which is the count of critical projects successfully finished that would have otherwise been delayed or impossible due to budget constraints. The app could also gather Impact Surveys to capture post-project feedback from non-profits.</p>
<h2>For Employees</h2>
<p>Success here can be seen through the employee participation rates. Track the hours volunteered, noting the total number of hours logged per employee, department, and company-wide. Additionally, the app could monitor employee engagement and satisfaction through surveys, looking for a lift in morale and a stronger connection to the company&#39;s social responsibility mission.</p>
<h2>For the Company (as a CSR)</h2>
<p>Community investment can be tracked by reporting on the total monetary value of all pro-bono work. Or measure brand reputation over time.</p>]]></potential_impact>
        <problem_statement>Non-profit organizations operate on tight budgets, often lacking access to specialized professional skills in areas like marketing, IT, finance, and legal services. This "expertise gap" limits their ability to scale their operations, enhance their reach, and maximize their social impact.&#13;
&#13;
Simultaneously, many corporate employees are eager to contribute to social causes in a meaningful way that utilizes their unique professional talents, beyond just making cash donations. However, they lack a structured, efficient platform to find and engage in these short-term, high-impact pro-bono opportunities. The core problem is the disconnect between the supply of valuable professional skills and the demand from the non-profit sector.&#13;
&#13;
A company could install this application and employees could go on it and advertise their work-related or even personal skills and the company could then go to local non-profit organizations and show them this listing of skills that they could provide.&#13;
Or non-profits can post jobs and it will automatically find matching employees according to their listed skills.</problem_statement>
        <project_name>ImpactConnect - Skills for Social Good</project_name>
        <solution_proposal><![CDATA[<h2><strong>How do you envision the ideal solution to this  problem?</strong></h2>
<p> </p>
<h3>Which ServiceNow products or capabilities would be used?</h3>
<p></p><ul><li>Service Portal or Employee Center: We&#39;d use this to create a clean, easy-to-use website for non-profits to find skillsets and for employees to post what they can provide.</li><li>Flow Designer: Automations so when a non-profit posts a gig looking for a writer, the system automatically finds employees with &#34;writing&#34; in their skills and sends them a notification.</li><li>Performance Analytics/Reporting: This would power the dashboards that show all the stats, like hours volunteered and value created, giving everyone a real-time look at the impact.</li><li>Task and Time Card Management: We can use some simple task and time-tracking features to make it easy for employees to log their hours on a project.</li><li>Integrations: This would be super helpful for automatically checking if a non-profit is legit by connecting to an external database of registered charities.</li><li>Notifications: This handles simple, automatic emails and alerts to keep everyone in the loop about project applications and updates.</li></ul>
<p> </p>
<hr style="border-top: 3px solid #bbb;" />
<h3>Are there any technical dependencies for the proposed solution?</h3>
<p></p><p>An external connection to verify non-profit status of any company trying to utilize the service.</p>
<p>The instance used should be attached to the company SSO so that users are verified.</p>
<p> </p>
<hr style="border-top: 3px solid #bbb;" />
<h3>What challenges would you foresee in implementing this idea?</h3>
<p></p><p>The biggest is just getting it off the ground; you need enough interesting projects from non-profits to attract employees, and enough skilled employees to attract the non-profits.</p>
<p>Another challenge is helping non-profits define their needs clearly. A request like &#34;build me a new website&#34; is too big, so we&#39;d need to help them break it down into smaller, manageable gigs. An approval process or clarification process is probably needed but would cause additional overhead because &#34;requirements writer&#34; is itself a skill that could be used ¯\_(ツ)_/¯ </p>
<p>We&#39;d also have to think about quality control. What happens if the work isn&#39;t what the non-profit expected? A simple rating system would help, but we might need a way to handle the occasional dispute.</p>]]></solution_proposal>
        <state>submitted</state>
        <sys_class_name>x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>earl.duque</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-10-02 05:18:32</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>b6f854d283d0f610e6db99d6feaad34c</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>1</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>ImpactConnect - Skills for Social Good</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Hack4Good Idea Submission" source="x_snc_hack4good_0">95b5d2b7938832108543b2597bba109c</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Hack4Good Idea Submission">95b5d2b7938832108543b2597bba109c</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal_b6f854d283d0f610e6db99d6feaad34c</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>earl.duque</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-10-02 05:18:34</sys_updated_on>
    </x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal>
</record_update>
