<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal">
    <x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <focus_area>disaster</focus_area>
        <notes/>
        <participation>yes</participation>
        <potential_impact><![CDATA[<p>You could prove the program is working by tracking how many check-ins are completed. </p>
<p>The app would count every time a call helped catch a problem early, like a fall or illness, preventing a bigger emergency.</p>
<p>It would show how many volunteers are involved and how much time they are giving to their community.</p>
<p>Most importantly, it would help older residents feel safer and less lonely.</p>]]></potential_impact>
        <problem_statement>Social isolation is a critical health concern, particularly for elderly and vulnerable individuals living alone. This isolation can lead to loneliness, depression, and preventable medical emergencies going unnoticed. Community organizations that want to help often lack the tools to manage and scale their outreach efficiently, relying on manual methods like spreadsheets, which make it difficult to ensure consistent, reliable wellness checks for everyone in need.</problem_statement>
        <project_name>Community Circle</project_name>
        <solution_proposal><![CDATA[<h2><strong>How do you envision the ideal solution to this  problem?</strong></h2>
<p> </p>
<h3>Which ServiceNow products or capabilities would be used?</h3>
<p></p><p>App Engine Studio: To quickly build the basic app and its database tables.</p>
<p>Playbooks: To create a simple, step-by-step guide for volunteers to follow during their calls.</p>
<p>Now Mobile: To give volunteers an easy-to-use phone app to see their call list and record their updates.</p>
<p>Workspace: To give the main organizer a dashboard to see everything at once, especially any urgent alerts.</p>
<p> </p>
<hr style="border-top: 3px solid #bbb;" />
<h3>Are there any technical dependencies for the proposed solution?</h3>
<p></p><p>Everything can be done OOB in ServiceNow! For enhancements, could integrate automatic text message reminders.</p>
<p> </p>
<hr style="border-top: 3px solid #bbb;" />
<h3>What challenges would you foresee in implementing this idea?</h3>
<p></p><p>Keeping Info Safe: The app stores private information about vulnerable people, so it must be extremely secure to protect their privacy.</p>
<p>Making it Easy for Volunteers: The phone app needs to be super simple, otherwise volunteers who aren&#39;t tech-savvy might not use it.</p>
<p>Handling Emergencies: You need a clear, foolproof plan for what a volunteer should do if they find a serious problem. The app must make this process easy to follow.</p>
<p>Trusting Volunteers: You need a good system in the real world for vetting volunteers to make sure they are trustworthy people.</p>]]></solution_proposal>
        <state>submitted</state>
        <sys_class_name>x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-10-03 00:55:31</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>200bec22c3103610e89b341d050131e6</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>1</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>Community Circle</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Hack4Good Idea Submission" source="x_snc_hack4good_0">95b5d2b7938832108543b2597bba109c</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Hack4Good Idea Submission">95b5d2b7938832108543b2597bba109c</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal_200bec22c3103610e89b341d050131e6</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-10-03 00:55:33</sys_updated_on>
    </x_snc_hack4good_0_hack4good_proposal>
</record_update>
